Hi guys. Many friends want to take a look at the babies of Xi Xi and Gua Gua
See, right here
They are in a different cell now
Now there's only... only two left
There was one...
crushed by the female rat when it was even smaller
I forgot which one it was
In fact, they are not Whitey's babies
They are Gua Gua's
Xi Xi was pregnant when still with Gua Gua. I didn't notice then
Then I put Xi Xi with Whitey
Now I know after they were born
They are Whi... Gua Gua's
See? This one is smaller
See? It got some genetic inheritance from its mom
For example, the fur tips are white
The belly is also white
But it's still black inside
Let's show it to Gua Gua, who must be very happy
Look. This is Gua Gua
This is its son
Are they alike?
Come on, take a look at your son
Did you know you are a dad now?
Whoa. Why are you biting your dad? You'll be beaten
Gua Gua doesn't cooperate at all
Put it back
Or Gua Gua's going to be angry
It wants to bite me. See?
You're so bad
Why are you so bad? Don't bite me
If you bite me, you'll be... You know
Xi Xi has grown new teeth now
Look at its teeth
Super beautiful now, isn't it?
Next time, let's give it a husband
to replace Gua Gua
We don't need Gua Gua anymore
Its body is so white
Even Whitey is not as white
Xi Xi is even whiter
Its having good food and sleep recently
Look
Even the skin is getting better
As there's elephant grass to eat now
Put it...
here
Get up, Whitey
Say hi to the audience
Look at you. You are now yellow
Should be two or three years old now. Over three
Next time... You'll take a shower
Its body is getting yellow. See?
Not clean for sure
Why are you so scared?
I'm just taking you up
I won't do anything to you
Put you back
All right. That's all for today's video
The babies of Xi Xi and Gua Gua
are now raised by a nanny rat
Let's not interrupt them